jobs.ac.uk 2019-04-04

# Privacy Policy | Legal - jobs.ac.uk

## JOBSEEKERS

This part of the Privacy Policy is specific to Jobseekers. 

jobs.ac.uk is committed to ensuring your privacy is protected. When signing up for a jobs.ac.uk account or our Jobs by Email service, we collect your name, email address, location and job searching preferences. We will not contact you other than to send you the jobs by email bulletins you have subscribed for or any email communications that you have consented to from us around company news, conferences, meetings or events. We will not distribute any of the details you provide for marketing purposes to a third party. We have put in place suitable security procedures to safeguard your information. 

You can withdraw your consent for the communications above at any time by editing your profile or clicking the relevant unsubscribe link in any emails received. 

Our website uses Google Maps API(s) and as such you are subject to [ Google’s Privacy Policies ](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

### Cookies

The jobs.ac.uk Website uses cookies to provide enhanced functionality and to gather information about how the site is being used to help us continually improve the user experience. For more details about what cookies are, the cookies that we use and how to disable them, please see our Cookie Policy. 

### Your Rights

Under the General Data Protection Regulations and Data Protection Act 2018 you have a number of important rights free of charge. You have the right to: 

  * Be informed of how we collect and use your personal data
  * Access your personal data
  * Require us to correct any mistakes in the data we hold on you
  * Require the erasure of personal data concerning you in certain situations
  * Restrict our processing of your personal data in certain circumstances
  * Receive your personal data in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and have the right to transmit those data to a third party in certain situations 
  * Object in certain situations to our continued processing of your personal data or at any time to processing of your personal data for direct marketing 
  * Object to decisions being taken by automated means which produce legal effects concerning you or similarly significantly affect you 

To exercise any of these rights please find out more [ here ](https://warwick.ac.uk/services/idc/dataprotection/datasubjectrights). If a subject access request is made and the request for access is clearly unfounded or excessive, the University reserves the right to refuse to comply with the request in these circumstances. 

You can also amend your details or delete your account at any time by logging into your jobs.ac.uk account and updating your details online. 

### How to Contact Us

We hope that our Data Protection Officer (DPO) can resolve any query, concern or complaint you raise about our use of your personal data on the contact details below: 

Ms Anjeli Bajaj (DPO) can be contacted via e-mail at [ infocompliance@warwick.ac.uk ](mailto:infocompliance@warwick.ac.uk)

or write to: 

The Data Protection Officer  
Information and Data Compliance Team  
University of Warwick  
University House  
Coventry  
CV4 8UW  

The GDPR and DPA 2018 also gives you the right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner who may be contacted at [ https://ico.org.uk/concerns/ ](https://ico.org.uk/concerns/) or telephone: 0303 123 1113. 

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and any updates will be uploaded to this page. This statement was last updated on 27th September 2018.
